export default [
  {
    question: "What is Harry Potter's middle name?",
    answerChoices: ['Sammy', 'James', 'Peter', 'Sirius'],
    correctAnswer: 'James'
  },
  {
    question: 'What division in the Ministry of Magic does Arthur Weasley work in?',
    answerChoices: [
      'Department of Mysteries',
      'Magical Law Enforcement Patrol',
      'Misuse of Muggle Artefacts Office',
      'Improper Use of Magic Office'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Misuse of Muggle Artefacts Office'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where did the passage beneath the one-eyed witch statue lead to?',
    answerChoices: ['Honeydukes', 'Shrieking Shack', 'The Three Broomsticks', 'The Room of Requirements'],
    correctAnswer: 'Honeydukes'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many sickles are in a galleon?',
    answerChoices: ['20', '18', '17', '29', '15'],
    correctAnswer: '17'
  },
  {
    question: 'What incantation fixes a broken Vanishing Cabinet?',
    answerChoices: ['Harmonia Nectere Passus', 'Anteoculatia', 'Ventus Duo', 'Reparo'],
    correctAnswer: 'Harmonia Nectere Passus'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many Weasley children are there?',
    answerChoices: ['4', '8', '10', '7', '6'],
    correctAnswer: '7'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of dragon did Harry have to face during the Triwizard Tournament?',
    answerChoices: ['Hungarian Horntail', 'Chinese Fireball', 'Swedish Shortsnout', 'Common Welsh Green'],
    correctAnswer: 'Hungarian Horntail'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where was the original headquarters for the Order of the Phoenix?',
    answerChoices: ['The Burrow', '12 Grimmace Place', '24 Nurmengard Way', '12 Grimmauld Place'],
    correctAnswer: '12 Grimmauld Place'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are NOT sweets sold at Honeydukes?',
    answerChoices: ['Toothflossing Stringmints', 'Cockroach Clusters', 'Pepper Imps', 'Broomstick Crunches'],
    correctAnswer: 'Broomstick Crunches'
  },
  {
    question: "What is Voldemort's wand made out of?",
    answerChoices: ['Ash', 'Hawthorn', 'Yew', 'Vine wood'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yew'
  },
  {
    question: 'What did the Marauders call Snape to make fun of him?',
    answerChoices: ['Sev', 'Slytherus', 'Prince', 'Snivellus'],
    correctAnswer: 'Snivellus'
  },
  {
    question: "What is the occupation of Hermione's parents?",
    answerChoices: ['Doctors', 'Dentists', 'Professors', 'Lawyers'],
    correctAnswer: 'Dentists'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year was Hagrid in when he was expelled from Hogwarts?',
    answerChoices: ['First', 'Fourth', 'Sixth', 'Third'],
    correctAnswer: 'Third'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was headmaster at Hogwarts before Albus Dumbledore?',
    answerChoices: ['Phineas Nigellus Black', 'Minerva McGonagall', 'Newton Scamander', 'Armando Dippet'],
    correctAnswer: 'Armando Dippet'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you breed a basilisk?',
    answerChoices: [
      'They occur naturally',
      'Hatch a chicken egg underneath a toad',
      'Make a sacrifice in the Chamber of Secrets',
      'Ask Hagrid'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Hatch a chicken egg underneath a toad'
  },
  {
    question: "What shape did Seamus Finnigan's boggart take?",
    answerChoices: ['Banshee', 'Bloodstained, bandaged mummy', 'Giant cobra', 'Dementor'],
    correctAnswer: 'Banshee'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is the Hufflepuff common room located near?',
    answerChoices: ['Green houses', 'Astronomy tower', 'Great Hall', 'Kitchens'],
    correctAnswer: 'Kitchens'
  },
  {
    question: 'All this time?',
    answerChoices: ['Always'],
    correctAnswer: 'Always'
  }
];
